const questionsData = [
    {
      section: "Section 1",
      questions: [
        {
          questionText:
            "During a team meeting, a team member asks about the measurements that will be used on the project to judge performance. The team member feels that some of the measures related to the activities assigned to him are not valid measurements. The project is BEST considered in what part of the project management process?",
          options: [
            "Initiating",
            "Executing",
            "Monitoring & Controlling",
            "Closing"
          ],
          correctAnswer: "Executing",
          explanation:
            "The question states that team member feels some of the measures on his activities are not valid. Therefore, he must be working during the executing phase of the project where project deliverables are produced and project members perform most of their assigned work."
        },
  
        {
          questionText:
            "Your project management plan results in a project schedule that is too long; if the project network diagram cannot change but you have extra personnel resources, what is the BEST thing to do?",
          options: [
            "Fast track the project.",
            " Level the resources. ",
            "Crash your project",
            "Monte Carlo analysis."
          ],
          correctAnswer: "crash you project",
          explanation:
            "Because, in the first sentence, it is mentioned that the schedule is too long, therefore the aim is to make a shorter schedule. And in the second sentence, it is mentioned that you have extra personnel resources."
        },
  
        {
          questionText:
            "Gabriel is a project manager working on a construction project. Your agile team needs to establish a product increment at the end of every iteration. He wants to make sure that the team has adequate time before the demonstration. He suggests his team to follow; select the most appropriate response.",
          options: [
            "To track different tasks with a project management plan",
            "For conducting the demonstration, the team should create a user story",
            "Take some time and delay the demonstration to the next iteration",
            "Ask for help to handle the demonstration"
          ],
          correctAnswer:
            "For conducting the demonstration, the team should create a user story",
          explanation:
            "The creation of a user story to demonstrate the product increment developed in the iteration allows the team to allocate dedicated time to get prepared for the demonstration. The sprint demo shouldn’t take up too much of a Scrum team’s time. Time shouldn’t be spent putting long slide decks together – the focus should be on the work and the demonstration should only include stories that meet the team’s definition of Done. Typically, a day or two before the end of the sprint, a project manager holds a short demo run-through and makes notes on anything they need to set up in order to make the demo flow well."
        },
  
        {
          questionText:
            "A project team is participating in a brainstorming meeting for a project. The project is in the planning phase. The team is trying to determine the current and preferred project stakeholder engagement levels and analyzing the gaps between these two states. They are also discussing different approaches and strategies that can be adopted to close these gaps. This relates to which of the following processes?",
          options: [
            "Develop project charter",
            "Monitor stakeholder engagement",
            "Identify stakeholders",
            "Plan stakeholder engagement"
          ],
          correctAnswer: "Plan stakeholder engagement",
          explanation: "Plan stakeholder engagement"
        },
  
        {
          questionText:
            "While the five process groups are typically completed in order, they often overlap with each other throughout the project. Which two process groups do not overlap unless a project is canceled?",
          options: [
            "Initiating and Closing",
            "Initiating and Executing",
            "Initiating and Monitoring and Control",
            "Planning and Closing"
          ],
          correctAnswer: "Initiating and Closing",
          explanation: "Initiating and Closing"
        },
  
        {
          questionText:
            "Gary is a project manager wrapping up the construction of a new office building. He creates several documents during this process. Which of the following is not applicable to the Control Procurements process?",
          options: [
            "Lessons learned documentation",
            "Formal written notice of acceptance of deliverables",
            "Closed contracts",
            "Project charter"
          ],
          correctAnswer: "Project charter",
          explanation: "Project charter"
        },
  
        {
          questionText:
            "All of the following are characteristics of a project, EXCEPT:",
          options: [
            "Has a definite beginning and end",
            "Temporary",
            "Progressively elaborated",
            "Ongoing Effort"
          ],
          correctAnswer: "Ongoing Effort",
          explanation: "Ongoing Effort"
        },
  
        {
          questionText:
            "You are the Project Manager for KT’s Lumber Yard. You are trying to forecast estimates for the last phase of the project you are currently working on. Based on the performance of the project to date, which formula can be used to estimate the total value of the project when completed assuming similar variances will not occur?",
          options: [
            "ETC = (BAC – EV)/CPI",
            "SV = EV – PV",
            "CPI = EV/AC",
            "EAC = AC + BAC – EV"
          ],
          correctAnswer: "EAC = AC + BAC – EV",
          explanation: "EAC = AC + BAC – EV"
        },
  
        {
          questionText:
            "Project costs are estimated for all project activities and aggregated to establish a cost baseline. Which of the following statements about the cost baseline is NOT true?",
          options: [
            "The project cost performance is measured against the cost baseline",
            " The cost baseline is an output of the determine budget process",
            "The cost baseline includes all authorized budgets including management reserves",
            "The cost baseline is in the form of an ‘S’ curve"
          ],
          correctAnswer:
            "The cost baseline includes all authorized budgets including management reserves",
          explanation:
            "The cost baseline includes all authorized budgets including management reserves"
        },
  
        {
          questionText:
            "The costs on a project are typically classified as direct and indirect costs. The cost of electric utilities for the office would be considered as:",
          options: [
            "An indirect cost",
            "Appraisal cost",
            "A specific cost",
            "A direct cost"
          ],
          correctAnswer: "An indirect cost",
          explanation: "An indirect cost"
        },
        {
          questionText:
            "The requirements elicitation team has obtained a large number of ideas during sessions to gather product and project requirements. Which of the following techniques is best suited to have these ideas sorted into groups for review and analysis?",
          options: [
            "Control chart",
            "Venn diagram",
            "Affinity diagram",
            "Brainstorming"
          ],
          correctAnswer: "Affinity diagram",
          explanation: "Affinity diagram"
        },
  
        {
          questionText:
            "Which of these precedence relationships is least commonly used in Precedence Diagramming Method?",
          options: [
            "Start to Start",
            "Finish to Finish",
            "Finish to Start",
            "Start to Finish"
          ],
          correctAnswer: "Start to Finish",
          explanation: "Start to Finish"
        },
  
        {
          questionText:
            "Terry is managing a healthcare software development project using state-of-the-art technology. Stakeholder management is very crucial for the success of this project. The stakeholder involvement and influence is significant on this project. During which of following project stages, stakeholder management will be the most challenging task for Terry?",
          options: [
            "Early during the project execution",
            "Towards the end of the project execution",
            "Towards the closure of the project",
            "Halfway through the project execution"
          ],
          correctAnswer: "Early during the project execution",
          explanation: "Early during the project execution"
        },
  
        {
          questionText:
            "All of the following are tools of the Control Schedule process EXCEPT:",
          options: [
            "Parametric estimating",
            "Modeling techniques",
            "Schedule compression",
            "Leads and lags"
          ],
          correctAnswer: "Parametric estimating",
          explanation: "Parametric estimating"
        },
        {
          questionText:
            "Sometimes the broader, more comprehensive summary activity is also referred to as:",
          options: [
            "Critical Activity",
            "Hammock Activity",
            "Milestone",
            "Group Task"
          ],
          correctAnswer: "Hammock Activity",
          explanation: "Hammock Activity"
        },
        {
          questionText:
            "Which strategy attempts to reduce the probability and/or the impact of a risk to the point where the risk can be accepted?",
          options: ["Mitigation", "Avoidance", "Acceptance", "Transfer"],
          correctAnswer: "Mitigation",
          explanation: "Mitigation"
        },
  
        {
          questionText:
            "Collect Requirements, Develop Schedule and Perform Qualitative Risk Analysis are all part of what process group?",
          options: [
            "Planning",
            "Scope Planning",
            "Monitor and Controlling",
            "Executing"
          ],
          correctAnswer: "Planning",
          explanation: "Planning"
        },
  
        {
          questionText:
            "John has just been assigned as the project manager of a project to develop a complex product. The project is in the Define Scope phase. Which of these tools / techniques will not be used by John in this phase?",
          options: [
            "Lateral thinking",
            "Process analysis",
            "Product breakdown",
            "Value engineering"
          ],
          correctAnswer: "Process analysis",
          explanation: "Process analysis"
        },
  
        {
          questionText:
            "The Project Managers have maximum authority in which type of organization?",
          options: [
            "Weak Matrix",
            "Strong Matrix",
            "Functional",
            "Balanced Matrix"
          ],
          correctAnswer: "Strong Matrix",
          explanation: "Strong Matrix"
        },
  
        {
          questionText:
            "Which of the following enterprise environmental factors is not applicable to the Plan Resource Management process?",
          options: [
            "Organizational culture and structure",
            "Existing human resources",
            "Personnel administration policies",
            "Lessons learned"
          ],
          correctAnswer: "Lessons learned",
          explanation: "Lessons learned"
        },
  
        {
          questionText:
            "While developing the project schedule, you find that the completion of a successor activity depends on the completion of its predecessor activity. What is this dependency called?",
          options: [
            "Start-to-Finish",
            "Start-to-Start",
            "Finish-to-Start",
            "Finish-to-Finish"
          ],
          correctAnswer: "Finish-to-Finish",
          explanation: "Finish-to-Finish"
        },
        {
          questionText:
            "Your company has temporarily assigned you to serve as a project manager at a company location outside your home country. While meeting with a vendor your first day on the job, you are presented with a gift. The corporate policy at the headquarters in your home country prohibits employees from accepting these types of gifts. However, as you are new to this location, you believe- but are not sure-that the local policy, as well as local custom may differ. How should you respond?",
          options: [
            "Provide a gift of similar value to the vendor at your next meeting.",
            "Accept the gift but do not tell anyone.",
            "Respectfully tell the vendor you are not sure of corporate policy, and will need to ask your management before you can accept gifts of any size.",
            "Accept the gift this time, but ask your manager about the local policy afterwards."
          ],
          correctAnswer:
            "Respectfully tell the vendor you are not sure of corporate policy, and will need to ask your management before you can accept gifts of any size.",
          explanation:
            "Respectfully tell the vendor you are not sure of corporate policy, and will need to ask your management before you can accept gifts of any size."
        },
  
        {
          questionText:
            "A Project manager estimates the work to be accomplished in the near term in detail, at a low level of the Work Breakdown structure (WBS); while he estimates work far in the future as WBS components, that are at a relatively high level of the WBS. What is this technique called?",
          options: [
            "Decomposition",
            "Rolling wave planning",
            "Scope Creep",
            "Earned value planning"
          ],
          correctAnswer: "Rolling wave planning",
          explanation: "Rolling wave planning"
        },
  
        {
          questionText: "The Manage Team process is part of what process group?",
          options: [
            "Planning",
            "Executing",
            "Monitoring and Controlling",
            "Closing"
          ],
          correctAnswer: "Executing",
          explanation: "Executing"
        },
  
        {
          questionText:
            "What is the traditional way to display a reporting structure among project team members?",
          options: [
            "Text-oriented role description",
            "Flowchart",
            "Hierarchical-type charts",
            "Matrix based responsibility chart"
          ],
          correctAnswer: "Hierarchical-type charts",
          explanation: "Hierarchical-type charts"
        },
  
        {
          questionText:
            "As part of the Define Scope process, a project manager documented the specific project assumptions associated with the project scope in the project scope statement. While reviewing this document, an experienced project manager pointed out that the project manager should also document:",
          options: [
            "The date on which the assumption becomes invalid.",
            "The assigned responsibility for each of the assumptions.",
            "The potential impact of the assumptions if they proved to be false.",
            "An Assumption Management Plan."
          ],
          correctAnswer:
            "The potential impact of the assumptions if they proved to be false.",
          explanation:
            "The potential impact of the assumptions if they proved to be false."
        },
  
        {
          questionText:
            "You are in the Validate Scope process of your electronic goods manufacturing project. While reviewing some products, you have noticed that the tolerance for one product is 0.01% less than what was listed in the requirements documentation. This deviation may not be a problem for the customers and it may not negatively impact the operations. What is your best immediate action in such a situation?",
          options: [
            "Notify the customers about the deviation",
            "Change the project management plan to allow for small deviation",
            "Reject all products and restart the project",
            "Discuss with your team about the quality testing"
          ],
          correctAnswer: "Notify the customers about the deviation",
          explanation: "Notify the customers about the deviation"
        },
  
        {
          questionText:
            "What is the MAIN reason for controlling the project scope?",
          options: [
            "To enable scope creep",
            "To prevent changes from affecting the project",
            "To ensure timely closure of the project.",
            "Preventing scope creep."
          ],
          correctAnswer: "Preventing scope creep.",
          explanation: "Preventing scope creep."
        },
  
        {
          questionText:
            "A project is contracted as a Time & Material (T&M) type of contract. The service provider initially estimates that the total effort involved would be about 1000 hours of effort. The project is contracted at a rate of US$ 75 per hour of effort. If the project ended up with 1200 hours of effort, what would the contract payout be.",
          options: ["US$ 75,000", "US$ 90,000", "US$ 82,500", "US$ 120,000"],
          correctAnswer: "US$ 90,000",
          explanation: "US$ 90,000"
        }
  
        // Add more questions for Section 1
      ]
    },
    {
      section: "Section 2",
      questions: [
        {
          questionText:
            "Your project management plan results in a project schedule that is too long; if the project network diagram cannot change but you have extra personnel resources, what is the BEST thing to do?",
          options: [
            "Fast track the project.",
            "Level the resources.",
            "Crash the project",
            "Monte Carlo analysis."
          ],
          correctAnswer: "Crash the project",
          explanation:
            "Because, in the first sentence, it is mentioned that the schedule is too long, therefore the aim is to make a shorter schedule. And in the second sentence, it is mentioned that you have extra personnel resources."
        },
        {
          questionText:
            "You have identified a risk that will negatively affect your security project. You and your team have decided to use an older encryption technology because of the high risk associated with the new technology. What type of risk strategy are you using?",
          options: ["Mitigation", "Exploitation", "Avoidance", "Transfer"],
          correctAnswer: "Avoidance",
          explanation: "Avoidance"
        },
  
        {
          questionText:
            "The project management team performed activities such as measuring examining and verifying to determine whether work and deliverables met requirements and product acceptance criteria. Which of the following choices refers to a different set of activities than the ones just mentioned?",
          options: ["Walkthroughs", "Prevention", "Inspection", "Reviews"],
          correctAnswer: "Prevention",
          explanation: "Prevention"
        },
  
        {
          questionText:
            "Perform Integrated Change Control includes several configuration management activities. Which of the following is not part of Perform Integrated Change Control?",
          options: [
            "Change request",
            "Configuration Verification",
            "Configuration Status Accounting",
            "Configuration Identification"
          ],
          correctAnswer: "Change request",
          explanation: "Change request"
        },
  
        {
          questionText:
            "A project manager needed to shorten a project schedule. He decided to apply crashing, a schedule compression technique. Which of the following activities would not be an example of crashing?",
          options: [
            "Bringing in additional resources",
            "Reducing project scope",
            "Paying to expedite delivery activities",
            "Approving overtime"
          ],
          correctAnswer: "Reducing project scope",
          explanation: "Reducing project scope"
        },
  
        {
          questionText:
            "A project to construct a high-rise building is progressing very well. Stakeholders are proactive in identifying issues related to the quality of the structure, walls and floors. As a project manager, you are conducting meetings to clarify or resolve their issues. Although, you are committed to manage stakeholders concerns, you learned that some critical issues need to be deferred to the next phase of the project for resolution. What should you do in this situation?",
          options: [
            "You must not defer any stakeholder issues but look for alternate methods",
            "You must escalate these issues to the sponsor for his advice",
            "You must work with stakeholders to defer those issues",
            "You must request the stakeholders to retract their issues"
          ],
          correctAnswer: "You must work with stakeholders to defer those issues",
          explanation: "You must work with stakeholders to defer those issues"
        },
  
        {
          questionText:
            "On a control chart, if six consecutive plot points are above the mean, then what can be established about the process?",
          options: [
            "The process is out of control",
            "The process will be out of control after plotting the seventh point.",
            "The process is in control",
            "Nothing can be established"
          ],
          correctAnswer: "Nothing can be established",
          explanation: "Nothing can be established"
        },
  
        {
          questionText:
            "During the Plan Risk Management process, assigning _____ will help you and the project team identify all important risks and work more effectively during the identification process.",
          options: [
            "risk factors",
            "blame",
            "risk mitigation plans",
            "risk categories"
          ],
          correctAnswer: "risk categories",
          explanation: "risk categories"
        },
  
        {
          questionText:
            "Which of the following is an output of the Create WBS process?",
          options: [
            "Scope baseline",
            "Project scope statement",
            "Decomposition",
            "Requirements documentation"
          ],
          correctAnswer: "Scope baseline",
          explanation: "Scope baseline"
        },
  
        {
          questionText:
            "Which of the following is a hierarchical representation of project risks?",
          options: [
            "Risk Register",
            "Risk Mitigation",
            "Risk categories",
            "Risk Breakdown Structure"
          ],
          correctAnswer: "Risk Breakdown Structure",
          explanation: "Risk Breakdown Structure"
        },
  
        {
          questionText:
            "A project can be authorized by any of the following except:",
          options: [
            "The project manager",
            "The PMO",
            "The sponsor",
            "The portfolio steering committee"
          ],
          correctAnswer: "The project manager",
          explanation: "The project manager"
        },
  
        {
          questionText: "Which term best describes the Identify Risks process?",
          options: ["Finite", "Redundant", "Iterative", "Inconsequential"],
          correctAnswer: "Iterative",
          explanation: "Iterative"
        },
  
        {
          questionText:
            "Sally’s project has got a huge number of key positive and negative stakeholders. It is very important to closely manage the influential negative stakeholders to ensure project’s success. Do the key positive stakeholders need to be managed as well?",
          options: [
            "No; more attention needs to be given to the key negative stakeholders.",
            "The positive stakeholders need to be closely managed as well since stakeholders’ needs and expectations change over time.",
            "Project stakeholders should not be classified as positive and negative stakeholders.",
            "Yes; positive stakeholders should be more closely managed than the negative stakeholders."
          ],
          correctAnswer:
            "The positive stakeholders need to be closely managed as well since stakeholders’ needs and expectations change over time.",
          explanation:
            "The positive stakeholders need to be closely managed as well since stakeholders’ needs and expectations change over time."
        },
  
        {
          questionText:
            "You have recently joined the a new company as a project manager. While reviewing the procurement plans for a project you will be taking over, you see that the company is considering using one of the most expensive manufacturers to provide certain equipment required for the project. While working with your previous employer, you used a different supplier for the same equipment, and paid significantly less for the equipment. Without telling your boss, you call the supplier you worked with previously for a quote. Have you violated the rule of keeping the proprietary information confidential?",
          options: [
            "Maybe. You need to talk to your boss first.",
            "No. There is no harm in sharing the information with your current employer, because you are no longer working for your old employer.",
            "Yes. The supply source is proprietary information and you should not contact the supplier.",
            "You have not violated any rule."
          ],
          correctAnswer: "You have not violated any rule.",
          explanation: "You have not violated any rule."
        },
  
        {
          questionText:
            "For any complex project, once the project stakeholders are identified, the next step is to classify these stakeholders based on their current and desired engagement levels. What is the benefit of classifying the project stakeholders?",
          options: [
            "To help identify the project scope",
            "To help populate the stakeholder register",
            "To help define an approach strategy",
            "It is a mandatory step in stakeholder analysis"
          ],
          correctAnswer: "To help define an approach strategy",
          explanation: "To help define an approach strategy"
        },
  
        {
          questionText:
            "A complicated software project was authorized by a project sponsor. However, the users who were intended to use the product found it very difficult to articulate their requirements. What technique can be employed to elicit requirements for such a project?",
          options: [
            "Job overlaying",
            "Hidden participant",
            "Job duplication",
            "Job shadowing"
          ],
          correctAnswer: "Job shadowing",
          explanation: "Job shadowing"
        },
  
        {
          questionText:
            "A fellow project manager is retiring and moving to the mountains, you will be taking over his project. Before he leaves he tells you the project is on schedule, but only because he has had to “put the hammer down” on his project team and push them relentlessly. Pushing the team to perform activities to accomplish project objectives is a part of:",
          options: [
            "Direct and Manage Project Work",
            "Monitor and Control Project Work",
            "Control Quality",
            "Control Scope"
          ],
          correctAnswer: "Direct and Manage Project Work",
          explanation: "Direct and Manage Project Work"
        },
  
        {
          questionText:
            "As part of EVM, a project manager is calculating the to-complete performance index (TCPI) based on EAC. The data that he has is: the budget at completion for the project is $ 100,000, the earned value for the project is $ 25,000, the actual costs to date are 40,000 and the estimate at completion is $ 115,000. What is the TCPI that he will obtain?",
          options: ["1.1", "0.9", "1", "0"],
          correctAnswer: "1",
          explanation: "1"
        },
  
        {
          questionText:
            "A project manager used a control chart to determine whether a process was stable or not, and to determine if its performance was predictable. He determined the upper and lower specification limits based on the contractual requirements. A set of eighteen data points were taken. Of these, 8 consecutive data points were above the mean. What can you say about such a process?",
          options: [
            "A process is considered as out of control if five consecutive data points are above or below the mean. Hence the process is out of control.",
            "A process is considered as out of control if six consecutive data points are above or below the mean. Hence the process is within control.",
            "A process is considered as being within control if less than half the data points are above or below the mean. Hence the process is within control.",
            "A process is considered as out of control if seven consecutive data points are above or below the mean. Hence the process is out of control."
          ],
          correctAnswer:
            "A process is considered as out of control if seven consecutive data points are above or below the mean. Hence the process is out of control.",
          explanation:
            "A process is considered as out of control if seven consecutive data points are above or below the mean. Hence the process is out of control."
        },
  
        {
          questionText:
            "As an experienced PMP, you have found that running a WBS meeting is tricky because you need to find a balance between decomposition and excessive decomposition. When items are excessively decomposed it leads all of the following, EXCEPT:",
          options: [
            "It breaks the 100% rule.",
            "Inefficient use of resources",
            "Non productive management effort",
            "Decreased efficiency when performing work"
          ],
          correctAnswer: "It breaks the 100% rule.",
          explanation: "It breaks the 100% rule."
        },
  
        {
          questionText:
            "A project manager determines that there are 15 communication channels in the project. The number of stakeholders in the project must then be:",
          options: [
            "15 stakeholders",
            "6 stakeholders",
            "8 stakeholders",
            "105 stakeholders"
          ],
          correctAnswer: "6 stakeholders",
          explanation: "6 stakeholders"
        },
  
        {
          questionText:
            "A key project in an organization has been ignored due to high travel expenses associated with the movement of subject matter experts and other specialists across various project locations. Which of the following will permit such a project to be taken up in a cost-efficient manner?",
          options: [
            "Management sign-off",
            "Negotiation",
            "Virtual teams",
            "Co-location"
          ],
          correctAnswer: "Virtual teams",
          explanation: "Virtual teams"
        },
  
        {
          questionText:
            "Two of your team members played the Mega Millions lottery and won! As much as they like working on your team, they have decided to retire. What plan should be updated?",
          options: [
            "Retirement Plan",
            "Resource Availability Document",
            "Communications Plan",
            "Staffing Management Plan"
          ],
          correctAnswer: "Staffing Management Plan",
          explanation: "Staffing Management Plan"
        },
  
        {
          questionText:
            "A team of engineers is reviewing a scatter diagram to determine how the changes in two variables in a new type of automobile tire are related. The closer points on the diagram are to a diagonal line, ______ .",
          options: [
            "the more likely a control group will be required",
            "the more closely they are related",
            "the less likely they are to be related",
            "the less likely a control group will be required"
          ],
          correctAnswer: "the more closely they are related",
          explanation: "the more closely they are related"
        },
  
        {
          questionText:
            "Jane has recently finalized her project management plan and has also got it approved. She is managing a complex manufacturing process improvement project. The project stakeholders’ continuous support and commitment is an absolute must for the success of the project. Which of the following are the most crucial stakeholder management processes at this stage?",
          options: [
            "Plan Stakeholder Engagement and Manage Stakeholder Engagement",
            "Identify Stakeholders and Plan Stakeholder Engagement",
            "Manage Stakeholder Engagement and Monitor Stakeholder Engagement",
            "Plan Stakeholder Engagement and Monitor Stakeholder Engagement"
          ],
          correctAnswer:
            "Manage Stakeholder Engagement and Monitor Stakeholder Engagement",
          explanation:
            "Manage Stakeholder Engagement and Monitor Stakeholder Engagement"
        },
  
        {
          questionText:
            "Select the best answer: Continuous process improvement reduces ____ and ____ , which allows processes to operate at increased levels of efficiency and effectiveness.",
          options: [
            "Process and policy overhead.",
            "Departmental and organization processes",
            "Cost and scope",
            "Waste and non-value added activities."
          ],
          correctAnswer: "Waste and non-value added activities.",
          explanation: "Waste and non-value added activities."
        },
  
        {
          questionText:
            "A project is contracted as a Cost-Plus-Fixed-Fee (CPFF) type of contract with a fee of 10% of estimated costs. The estimated cost is US$ 50,000. If the project comes in at US$ 75,000 with no changes in project scope, what would be the total cost of the contract?",
          options: ["US$ 55,000", "US$ 125,000", "US$ 75,000", "US$ 80,000"],
          correctAnswer: "US$ 80,000",
          explanation: "US$ 80,000"
        },
  
        {
          questionText:
            "Your project team members have just started to work together and are now adjusting their work habits and behaviors to support each other. Which stage of the Tuckman ladder has your team just entered?",
          options: ["Norming", "Performing", "Forming", "Storming"],
          correctAnswer: "Norming",
          explanation: "Norming"
        },
  
        {
          questionText:
            "In order to keep costs low, a project management team decided to apply statistical sampling while inspecting some of the work products. They decided to select 10 out of 50 engineering drawings for inspection. During which process should the sample frequency and sample size be determined?",
          options: [
            "Collect Requirements",
            "Plan Quality Management",
            "Control Quality",
            "Manage Quality"
          ],
          correctAnswer: "Plan Quality Management",
          explanation: "Plan Quality Management"
        },
  
        {
          questionText:
            "Where would you find a detailed list and description of specific project assumptions associated with the project?",
          options: [
            "Project charter",
            "Project scope statement",
            "Project configuration document",
            "Change management plan"
          ],
          correctAnswer: "Project scope statement",
          explanation: "Project scope statement"
        },
  
        {
          questionText:
            "Which of the following is not an activity related to the Direct and Manage Project Work process?",
          options: [
            "Inspect the project deliverables for completeness.",
            "Provide, train, and manage the team members assigned to the project.",
            "Create project deliverables to meet the planned project work.",
            "Perform activities to accomplish project objectives."
          ],
          correctAnswer: "Inspect the project deliverables for completeness.",
          explanation: "Inspect the project deliverables for completeness."
        },
  
        {
          questionText:
            "Your project sponsor has asked you to add 30% contingency to your project budget as a hedge against any unforeseen costs that could exceed the currently forecasted expenses, but has not provided any additional detail about why this is required. What do you do?",
          options: [
            "Add 30% to the management reserves.",
            "Ask the sponsor to elaborate the risks that are behind the request.",
            "Rebaseline the project budget.",
            "Add 30% to the total budget."
          ],
          correctAnswer:
            "Ask the sponsor to elaborate the risks that are behind the request.",
          explanation:
            "Ask the sponsor to elaborate the risks that are behind the request."
        }
        // Add more questions for Section 2
      ]
    }
    // Add more sections here
  ];
  
  export default questionsData;
  